//
//  TriviaQuestions.json
//  Trivia
//
//  Created by Alexis Orellano on 3/1/22.
//

{
    "results": [
        {
            "id": 0,
            "category": "Twice",
            "type": "multiple",
            "question": "What was the name of Twice's first album?",
            "correct": "Twicetagram",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Merry & Happy",
                "Formula of Love: 0+T=<3",
                "Eyes Wide Open",
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "category": "Twice",
            "type": "multiple",
            "question": "Which member of Stray Kids was in the Ooh Ahh music video?",
            "correct": "Bang Chan",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Seungmin",
                "Hyunjin",
                "Han",
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "category": "Twice"
            "type": "multiple",
            "question": "Who got eliminated in episode 6 of Sixteen?",
            "correct": "Momo",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Nayeon",
                "Tzuyu",
                "Mina",
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "category": "BTS"
            "type": "multiple",
            "question": "Who was the secret member of BTS?",
            "correct": "V",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "RM",
                "Jin",
                "J-hope",
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "category": "BTS"
            "type": "multiple",
            "question": "Which company rejected J-hope?",
            "correct": "JYP",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "YG",
                "SM",
                "HYBE",
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "category": "Blackpink"
            "type": "multiple",
            "question": "Who's idea was it for rose to audition?",
            "correct": "Her dad",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Her mom",
                "Her sister",
                "Her cousin",
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "category": "Twice",
            "type": "multiple",
            "question": "What is the best dancer in Twice?",
            "correct": "Momo",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Jihyo",
                "Mina",
                "Nayeon",
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "category": "Itzy",
            "type": "multiple",
            "question": "Which member of Itzy was on sixteen?",
            "correct": "Chaeryoung",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Yeji",
                "Yuna",
                "Ryujin",
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "category": "BTS"
            "type": "multiple",
            "question": "Who nickname is World Wide Handsome?",
            "correct": "Jin",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Suga",
                "Taehyung",
                "Jungkook",
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "category": "Free for All"
            "type": "multiple",
            "question": "Who is not Australian?",
            "correct": "Jennie",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Rose",
                "Bang Chan",
                "Felix",
            ]
        }
    ]
}
